Once you finish each project, you'll submit it to us and
Quando terminar um projeto, mande para a gente.
we'll send it back to you with feedback.
Vamos devolvê-lo com correções.
Your evaluation will tell you either that your project met our specifications
A avaliação dirá se o projeto atendeu nossas expectativas
or that it hasn't yet.
ou se ainda não atendeu.
However, you can submit each project as many times as you need to for
No entanto, você pode apresentar cada projeto quantas vezes precisar
it to meet our specifications.
para que ele atenda as expectativas.
We believe that projects are a super important part of your learning process
Os projetos são uma parte muito importante do aprendizado,
because that process of getting feedback and making changes in accordance with
porque receber avaliações e aplicar as correções pedidas
it, thing that you'll do in the real world all the time.
é algo que você vai fazer no mundo real o tempo todo.
No one, not even the most expert engineer,
Ninguém, nem mesmo o engenheiro mais experiente,
writes perfect code the first time around.
faz programas perfeitos logo de cara.
So we want you to get in the mindset and
Então queremos que você se acostume e pratique
practice of iterating on your work right now.
criar iterações do seu trabalho agora.